If I used one sentence to describe the last season
如果用一句话去表达上一集的话
It might be "taking the first step" or "searching for the unknown"
可能是迈出第一步或者是寻找未知
For Season 2, I think it is "choice"
第二次的话我觉得是选择
Choosing which route?
选择哪条线路
yes
耶
Choosing to continue climbing, or choosing to descend
选择继续攀爬还是选择下降哦哈哈哈
Inhale  exhale
吸气呼吸
Or choose a direction in life. It`s all about choices
或者选择生活方向都是选择
Do you trust this stopper（protection gear） ?
这个塞子你比较信任嘛
I don't really trust any of them
每个都不太信任
So I'm also thinking. which thing will I choose
所以我也在想到底哪个事情我会去选择
Or what is worth my focused effort.
或者是值得我去专注的做
Good ?
OK 了吗
I don't know
不知道呀
Maybe found the general meaning
可能找到了大概的意义
Maybe it is just searching for vitality
可能就是在寻找生命力吧
Ah, it's a bit high.
啊 有点高啊
Maybe it is that I want to challenge myself and stimulate my own nerves
可能就是我要去挑战刺激我自己的神经
Well done
做的好
So for Season two, I'm going rock climbing.
所以第二季我要去攀岩哦
Hard to step on
不好踩
Maybe climbing is challenging yourself at every single moment
可能攀岩在无时无刻的一直在挑战自己
The start is really hard
起步真的很难
And breaking through my own difficulties that attracts me more
然后突破自己的困难会比较吸引我
I feel climbing is a way of finding oneself.
我觉得攀岩是寻找自我的一种方式
Constantly exploring new realms
不断的探索心境吧
Living life to the extreme
活出生命的极致